Inari Expedition!
That's all!
Minami Dance and Inari, please!
Please give my regards to you!
We are the Inari Expedition!
Today, we have Captain Fujitani and Mr. Hikaru!
What will these two be doing?
Today's expedition is to introduce the Used Book Festival Great Records CD1!
Yes! Sounds fun!
At the moment, right, on the 9th floor of EBiz, it's a very popular annual event.
The Secondhand Book Festival and the Great Record CD1 are currently taking place on the 9th floor of EBiz!
I'd like you two to go there today.
You like books, right? Hikaru-san likes books too.
How are you feeling about books?
I love them.
My goal is to become a literary girl.
Sounds like something Hikaru would say.
But I aspire to be...
A literary girl.
No, that's what you say.
That's why.
That's why I'm a literary girl too.
I see.
You two have records?
Well, we're not really familiar with them, so... you know, it's probably a bit of a bargain, but...
I'm sure you'll find some bargains.
Jackets, you know?
That kind of thing.
We'll be looking at all sorts of things.
It's a bit of a quiet shop.
I can't make much noise.
So today we're going to go on a secret expedition.
If I shout too loud, it'll be rude and disturb other customers.
I can do it, Mr. Fujita. It's always good to be that loud.
I'm having a seizure.
I'm sorry, I'm having a seizure.
Let's go.
What's going on?
This is where they're holding the used book festival and the big record CD1.
It's a huge space.
We're going to take a look, so we can't make too much noise.
Everyone is looking quietly.
Let's have an exploratory meeting.
Let's start with Record 1.
Okay.
So it's like a sleep-wake-up surprise?
It's okay.
It doesn't have to be so quiet.
Let's go.
She says it's weird.
You're being conspicuous.
It's like we're trying to steal something, Mr. Fujitani.
There's a lot here, so if something catches your eye, pick it up.
There's Mr. Mis Misu Iwarosu, for example.
Shut up and follow me.
Do you know Hitoshi Ueki?
Yes, he was my friend. Do you know Hitoshi Ueki who follows me?
Yes, he was my friend.
Were you friends with him?
I miss him.
I remember playing with him in Chiba Park.
I have a CD I want to take with me. Can I bring it?
A CD you want to take with you?
I'm off.
There's my senior.
Oh? I've got a senior citizen.
I've got a senior.
But something's different.
But something's appealing to you.
When you feel it...
I'll put it out like this.
I see.
I can't say it like that.
You're thinking like this.
You're using it wrong.
You can use it like this.
You're always working so hard on the editing.
Listen to the song.
Don't use it as a line.
There's a lot of stuff here.
There are so many.
How many of these do you have?
This shop.
We have 36 shops all over the country.
36 shops nationwide.
36 shops?
36 shops? I have to say 36 shops.
But if I say the number 36, people will be surprised.
I have to say "36 stores", but if I say the number 36, it might startle people, so please be quiet.
Something's different.
It's cute.
The jacket looks stylish.
It's been a while.
Can I be serious?
I'm being serious.
It was near a shop I used to go to.
I used to look at it every day.
This jacket.
I thought, "It's been a long time.
Is it right to say "a long time"?
He looks like my grandpa.
He's so handsome.
He is.
Really? He's so handsome.
This one.
He's so hot.
I love the cover.
Bow range bong.
Jan-jan-jan-jan.
Dice Thing School Tragedy.
There's something after this.
Why, like that murder.
Okay, can we do the same pose then?
Yeah, sure.
I want this in my room.
Yeah, I know.
It's for decoration.
But they're really cute.
They're my type.
Here's a bit of trivia.
I heard there are 36 shops here that change places.
The hostages are very stylish.
The farthest one's in Okayama.
Don't say "Okayama" like it's a bad word.
Don't say "Okayama" like it's a word you shouldn't say.
There it is.
This one's nice too.
It's good.
It's nice.
What's more...
And what's more...
Romia and Gilliette.
Oh, nice.
This is so good.
I wonder if it's this one or the next one.
Oh, no, no, no, no, it's true.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It fits!
I thought it was the other way round, but it's a kiss, isn't it?
After kissing, which is it?
I don't usually leave money where it is. I won't get angry.
You're not mad?
What about you?
Comment!
I've got your idea.
Why?
Comment, please.
Tell us this one, too.
I like it.
You know what?
You know him?
I know it.
That's great.
The ones we choose together are the ones that show our individuality.
Is it really good?
But there's something different about it.
It's a variety.
Hikaru's has a certain... atmosphere.
Then I'll choose the atmosphere.
Choose seriously.
Here, this one.
It's like a Picasso.
It's from Picasso.
I don't even really know what it says.
It's like a Picasso painting.
I really like this one.
I know what Hikaru's is.
This one.
Is it Hikaru-ish?
It looks like Miu.
This one.
So...
We've come to a full phone shop.
Next door.
Next door, next door.
I don't know how to say it... it's like miscellaneous goods.
Sundries, really.
They sell all kinds of things.
20 Fulfon shops from all over the country.
Shops mainly in the Tohoku region.
Let's take a look.
Jump to Shinji-chan.
That's great.
You can't see the old jumps.
When did he jump?
1982.
I wonder what they were doing back then.
Let's have a look.
What's this?
Cobra.
Cat's Eye.
Captain Tsubasa...
Dr. Slump Orarechan.
I know Himeko.
High School Onimengumi.
Orare-chan, it's Kinnikuman.
Great, great, nostalgic...
This one's great too.
Okiyo-e
I like it.
You like it?
I like Katsushika Hokusai's paintings.
I like them.
I'll introduce you to my favorite painting.
This one.
Yes, yes, yes.
The most famous one.
I love it.
I love it. - I love it.
My mum gave me some of these chocolates once.
Oh, you have?
That's great.
You like them.
Surprisingly.
This one.
I like it.
I didn't know they sold these.
Do you read hard books?
No, but I don't read that many difficult ones.
What kind of books do you read?
Right now I'm reading The Anatomy of a Hyakunin Isshu (The One Hundred Tanka Poems).
About the meaning of the Hyakunin Isshu?
Yes. I'm reading the kind of book that explains them.
Knowing the meanings.
I see. Sounds interesting.
It's the kind of thing where you can find out about the reader's background.
Interesting.
That's great.
It's about your father.
It's called The Law of Women.
I found an autographed copy for sale.
You know, the eyeshadow beauties.
And our round faces.
Because we have round faces.
This kind of autumn/winter make-up...
You're amazing, aren't you, Ikko?
That's right, I have amazing makeup at home.
Oh, I see.
Do you sell these?
Only the 3 yen ones. I sold them.
I sold them.
I just thought...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't sell it.
It's like, "Don't sell it.
I'm gonna throw it on your back.
Cat, I'm not giving up.
I'll never get tired of it.
I made a mistake.
Ahhh...
The meaning is totally changing.
I made a mistake.
I've read this.
Sherlock Holmes.
I think it's different depending on who translates it.
I see.
I've read something called The Four Signs.
Shamrock Herbs. That's good.
Sounds interesting.
Great. Lovely.
I found some animal horoscopes.
It's really cool.
It's like, let's do it later.
Let's do it later.
They sell all kinds of stuff.
What's your dream?
My dream is...
Baroque in the forest.
We'll have a conversation about the title.
What's "Baroque in the Forest"?
You're playing highbrow, aren't you?
It's fun... and I'm looking forward to it.
I'm having too much fun. I'm having too much fun.
You know, it's great, and the best thing about it is that it feels like it.
I feel fine.
I'm sick.
I'm sorry, I can't hear you.
It's all in the bloodstream.
Who's your friend to say that?
Well, now that you've picked out your favourite book.
Let's take it back to the dressing room with the record.
Okay, I'm in.
Let's take it backstage.
It's okay to speak up now.
Let's listen to the record we borrowed.
I borrowed this.
Thank you.
Let's bow.
You don't know what this is, do you?
Yes, you do. Nice to meet you.
Even if it's early.
Let's ask.
After all, it's the first time.
But is something different?
While listening to this.
Read Katsushika Hokusai.
Doesn't this fit?
It's the same as CDs, isn't it? I'll treat it like one.
Let's go. It's my first time.
Okay, then, here we go.
This song is my favourite song. I love this song. I like this song.
I like this song.
I like this song. I like this song. Yeah ... Heh! Nice and funny Dancing School Tragedy too.
Oh, you're so big! Oh, wow.
That's Kyle's side.
It's a big one. It's a big one.
Can I put this down? That was intense.
That was intense.
That wasn't nice at all.
It was rocking.
It was a lot less tragic than it sounds.
It was a lot less tragic.
It was fury.
It was cool.
I like it.
Let's hear the last song, "Nyan-nyan-nyan" by Ano Ne-no-san.
Let's listen to Nyan Nyan Nyan.
Nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan nyan.
A cat.
Do you have a cat? Do you have a cat?
There are 12 types.
Do you have any rabbits?
Oh, no! No!
There are no rabbits in Sunday, but there are Sculpin!
Let's go, next preview.
I know! Did you know?
It's the one that went viral on TikTok.
Cat nyan nyan nyan dog wan wan wan.
What's that?
Frogs and agels go go go go!
On TikTok.
You scared the shit out of me.
What's the good word?
Cat nyan nyan nyan nyan.
That's right, just now.
Maybe it was you.
This meeting...
What a surprise!
Next day.
Yes, so today...
I went to the Blue Phone Festival and the Great Record CD Market.
That was a lot of fun.
Hey, it was a lot of fun.
Let me tell you about this annual and very popular event.
Yes, please.
Let me see this.
Every year.
You're looking at it like crazy, down there.
That's not like you.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
Two or three times every year.
Two or three times, maybe two or three times.
Two or three times a year.
Switch it up.
Like per facility.
We're reopening it twice.
The first one in 2024.
20 March.
I'm serious once more.
Until 20 March, there will be two product changes.
Because of the changeover...
It's the same no matter when you come.
I see.
If you come on that day, you never know when they'll be sold out.
The other thing is...
We have a lot of young customers.
It's easy for them to come.
They want to buy it.
Didn't I say what I wanted to buy?
I wrote it down.
That's all for today's expedition.
Are you all right? Anything on your mind?
Yes, I did.
Anything you didn't see?
No.
Let's go to the cafeteria with the others.
Yes!
Nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya nyanya
Bye-bye!